What I'll be demonstrating here is bicep incline dumbbell curls.
And, what you're going to do is put your bench on an incline.
And, then pretty much doing the same thing that you would do if you were standing or sitting as curling the dumbbell.
Still giving it a good flex of the bicep when you bring it up.
Flex it.
This action's a little harder, only because you're at an incline.
So, when you bring it down you still want to control the weight.
Because, you're at an incline that weight is kind of forcing itself down a little faster.
When you bring it up, again you want to keep putting tension on that bicep.
And, you can go ahead and alternate it or you can go ahead and do it at the same time.
You want to keep doing about three to about eight ten to reps. And, if you wanted to you can switch it up and you can do hammers inclined dumbbell curls.